Ningninghou: So here's the deal.
Ningninghou: Then let's scout the area first.
Ningninghou: Like this.
Ningninghou: Nan, you cover this area, okay?
Nan Nandu: Okay.
Jin Jinliang: Then I'll cover that area.
Ningninghou: You cover that area.
Ke Ke'ai: I'll search around the dining table.
He Heda: Then I'll take this area.
Countdown begins.
Ningninghou: Check that out too.
Dingdingdang: There's something under this table.
Li Liwo: There's a sound.
Li Liwo: Intruder!
Li Liwo: Someone's here!
Nan Nandu: Don't touch me!
Thirty seconds deducted.
Li Liwo: Someone's here!
He Heda: You just wait.
Li Liwo: What?
Li Liwo: Who's here?
Li Liwo: What's that sound?
Thirty seconds deducted.
Ah!
Li Liwo: What?
Li Liwo: What is that?
Li Liwo: Who's there?
Li Liwo: This is so scary!
Dingdingdang: Let's just be bold for once.
Dingdingdang: We're definitely failing this round anyway.
Dingdingdang: Hurry!
Dingdingdang: Just be bold and look!
Li Liwo: That's not right.
Jin Jinliang: Is there a key?
Thirty seconds deducted.
Li Liwo: It's over.
Li Liwo: This room is full of people.
Li Liwo: It's a Zombie Siege!
Li Liwo: Geez.
Countdown ended.
Challenge failed.
Please stay where you are.
Please wait three minutes for the countdown to restart.
He Heda: I mean, did you guys really not find a single bottle?
Ke Ke'ai: I found one.
Jin Jinliang: There are no bottles on my end.
Dingdingdang: There are no bottles on my side.
Dingdingdang: I checked the dining table.
Jin Jinliang: Come over here and look.
Jin Jinliang: There really are no bottles here.
Ningninghou: Okay.
Ningninghou: Then let's do this.
Ningninghou: I suspect someone saw it but didn't say anything.
Ningninghou: So for this round,
Ningninghou: let's switch places, okay?
Ningninghou: Let me search this side this round, alright?